<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hailey Ryerson&#39;s Github Site</title>
    <link>http://haileyryerson.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hailey Ryerson&#39;s Github Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://haileyryerson.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How is Paige Bueckers changing women’s basketball?</title>
      <link>http://haileyryerson.github.io/2021/04/21/2021-04-21-second-final-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://haileyryerson.github.io/2021/04/21/2021-04-21-second-final-project/</guid>
      <description>Paige Bueckers made history this past season, becoming the first freshman to win the Associated Press’s Player of the Year award and exceeding the expectations of everyone in the country, including head coach of UConn Geno Auriemma. Every player who has come through the Huskies program has been exceptional, but Bueckers took on a leadership role the first couple of games of her collegiate career. She was the first UConn player to score 30+ in three consecutive games and most points scored by a UConn player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who will win the 2021 NCAA D1 Women’s Volleyball Tournament?</title>
      <link>http://haileyryerson.github.io/2021/04/01/hailey-ryerson-s-spmc-350-final-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://haileyryerson.github.io/2021/04/01/hailey-ryerson-s-spmc-350-final-project/</guid>
      <description>Note to the readers: this analysis was done during the week of March 29th rankings.
With weeks away from the first serve, 48 teams will travel to the midwest as Omaha, Nebraska will host the entire tournament. The tournament will take place at CHI Health Center from April 14-24. Covid-19 cancellations or poseponents have played a big factor in this unique season.
All eyes are on the Big Ten schools, as anyone of them could walk away with the trophy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hailey Ryerson&#39;s Blog</title>
      <link>http://haileyryerson.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://haileyryerson.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Hailey Ryerson and I&amp;rsquo;m a sophomore at the University of Nebraska-Lincoln studying Sports Media and Broadcasting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
